<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shuruat</string>
    <string name="SHURUT_APP">SHURUAT</string>
    <string name="heading">&quot;Creating pathways to academic excellence.&quot;</string>
    <string name="Login">REGISTERED USER LOGIN</string>
    <string name="New_Register">NEW USER REGISTRATION</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="Home">HOME</string>
    <string name="aboiut_us">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="CONTACT">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="Profile">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="WELCOME">WELCOME TO</string>
    <string name="content">Shuruat is an app designed to help the nearly 500 million+ rural women and 20 million small and unorganized businesses across the country get access to financial assistance through NBFCs, providing financial literacy especially in the areas of starting small businesses, retail investing. The app also comes with the added features of helping users navigate and create awareness about government schemes and policies. This app has been created and is being managed by IgniteIndia led by two teenagers- Vivaan Garg and Avaya Aggarwal</string>
    <string name="content2">\“Unleashing the vast human capital of India by providing financial assistance, literacy and access to government schemes to rural women and small businesses\”</string>
    <string name="powered">Powered by Ignite India</string>
    <string name="submit">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="forget">FORGET PASSWARD?</string>
    <string name="New_Registration">New Registration</string>
    <string name="Submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="finacal">Briefly explain why you require financial assistance</string>
    <string name="QUATE">\“Economic growth without the growth of the poorest of the poor isn’t not growth at all \” - Amartya Sen
</string>
    <string name="contactmait">  Maharaja Agrasen Institute of  Technology</string>
    <string name="postal">Maharaja Agrasen Institute of Technology  PSP Area, Plot No. 1, Sector-22, Rohini,  Delhi-110086  INDIA.</string>
    <string name="phone"> PHONE:-</string>
    <string name="number">91-8448186942</string>
    <string name="email">  Email address:-</string>
    <string name="id">mait@mait.ac.in</string>
    <string name="copy">© 1999 Maharaja Agrasen Institute of Technology, New Delhi. All Rights Reserved.</string>
    <string name="submit_now">submitnow</string>
    <string name="About_home">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="MISSON">OUR MISSION</string>
    <string name="VISON">OUR VISION</string>
    <string name="mission_content">At Shuruat, our mission is to empower financially challenged students by providing them with the necessary tools, resources, and support to overcome financial barriers and pursue their educational dreams. We are dedicated to streamlining the process of connecting students to financial assistance, creating a comprehensive database that enables organizations and institutions to enhance access to education. Through collaboration and advocacy, we aim to create a more equitable educational landscape where every student has the opportunity to thrive. Our mission is to be a catalyst for change, breaking down barriers and transforming lives through the power of education.</string>
    <string name="vision.">OUR VISION</string>
    <string name="vision_content">Our vision is to democratize access to finance and financial literacy across India. The female labor force participation rate for India is less than 25% for the year 2023. One of our core beliefs is that India will only transition from a developing to a developed economy by achieving total and complete gender equity; therefore this app has a special emphasis on increasing access to finance for rural women and making them self-reliant by fostering entrepreneurship </string>
    <string name="login_regis">REGISTERED USER</string>
    <string name="Extra">TODO</string>
    <string name="logo">TODO</string>
    <string name="image_string">image_string</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="aplly">APPLICATION FORM</string>
    <string name="personal">1. Personal Information</string>
    <string name="edu">2. Educational Details:</string>
    <string name="fin">3. Financial Information:</string>
    <string name="sch">Details of any Scholarships or Grants received:</string>
    <string name="re">4. Briefly explain why you require financial assistance and how it will benefit your educational journey:</string>
    <string name="otp">We will send you an One Time Password on this mobile number</string>
    <string name="otp_1">Enter The OTP sent to Entered Number</string>
    <string name="appl">Continued to Application Form........</string>
    <string name="forgot_pass">FORGOT PASSWORD?</string>
    <string name="forgot_p">Enter the Email address associated with your account</string>
    <string name="send_forgot">SEND</string>

</resources>